情书
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
presisco
校对
特效
presisco
压制
你闭眼了!
You blinked!
我们再拍一张吧
Let's just take another one.
哦, 等下
Oh, wait.
用一个漂亮的背景合影如何?
What if we get a shot with the beautiful view behind us?
快点, 史蒂文!
Come on, Steven!
说 "奶酪"
Say "cheese."
奶酪!
Cheese!
怎么样?
Did it do it?
我不知道
I don't know.
再按一次
Press it again.
我一直在按啊
I've been pressing it.
你们好可爱啊
You guys look cute.
杰米!
Jamie!
怎么样 史蒂文? 好久不见
What's up, Steven? Long time no see.
我...的...天!
Oh...My...Gosh!
杰米, 这是康妮
Jamie, this is Connie.
你好, 康妮
Greetings, Connie.
那么. 你之前都在哪?
So, where you been at?
哦, 你知道的, 就是花了点时间
Oh, you know, just spent some time
逛逛大制作诞生的地方
where all the big pictures are made.
呃, 是哪?
Uh, where's that?
就是个小地方, 叫...
Just a little place called...
堪堪堪萨斯
Kannnnsas.
噢! 你是想当演员吗?
Oh! Are you an aspiring thespian?
当然 是 的
Why, a-yes, I am.
喔, 我还不知道你想当演员啊
Wow. I didn't know you wanted to be an actor.
那是因为...
That's because...
我擅长表演
I'm very good at acting.
这就是是你戴写着 "电影明星"
Is that why you're wearing those cool glasses
的炫酷眼镜的原因?
that say "movie star"?
呃...其实...不是
Uh...Well...No.
这只是从纪念品店买的
I just bought these at a souvenir shop.
我怀念当个平凡邮递员的日子,
I missed being a regular old mailman,
所以我回来了
so I just came back.
而且, 呃, 我走的这段时间你有收到很多邮件
And, uh, you got a lot of mail while I was gone.
看来邮政服务一直很懈怠啊
Looks like the postal service has been slacking off.
杰米是唯一一个知道我住哪的邮递员
Jamie's the only mailman that knows where I live.
我还需要很多的签收
I'm gonna need a lot of signatures, as well.
你的关节居然没声音
Your knuckles are so quiet.
我的手很讲礼节
My hands are polite.
哦, 石榴
Oh. Garnet.
石榴出水的场景源自007系列电影"Dr.No"
嗨, 石榴!
Hi, Garnet! Hello, Garnet!
谁是石--
Who's gar--
你好
Howdy.
你在干哈, 石榴?
Whatcha up to, Garnet?
我刚才在海底
I was just at the bottom of the ocean
寻找青金石和铁石英的踪迹
checking for signs of Lapis and Jasper.
怎么样?
Any luck?
没有
Nope.
你怎么可能游到海底?
How were you able to swim to the bottom of the ocean?
很简单
It was easy.
我擅长游泳
I'm a really good swimmer.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
石榴去除体表水分的动作源自 "歪小子斯科特"
呃, 史蒂文
Uh, Steven,
为什么你会收到那么多盒海人?
why did you receive so many boxes of sea pals?
呃, 我一开始只订了一盒, 但一直没收到
Uh, I ordered one at first, but it never showed up.
所以我反复下单
So I kept ordering.
你要建个农场吗?
Are you going to start a farm?
不
No.
我要放生他们
I'm gonna set them free.
回到大海!
Into the sea!
杰米!
Jamie!
嗨, 史蒂文
H-hi. Steven.
你不会带来了更多的的海人吧?
You didn't bring more sea pals?
什么? 不, 我只是, 呃...
What? No, I just came to, uh...
那是什么?
What's that?
呃, 这是...呃...
Uhh, it's...Uhh...
给你!
Here!
但这是...什么?
But what is...It?
杰米!
Jamie!
石榴! 石榴! 石榴!
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
最不可思议的事情发生了!
The most unbelievable thing has happened!
你绝对会被吓死的!
You'll absolutely die of shock!
我很忙, 史蒂文
I'm busy, Steven.
但你收到了一封信!
But you got a letter!
读一下
Read it.
" 致石榴... "
"To Garnet..."
" 当我目睹你如远古海洋仙女般站起,  "
"When I saw you rise like an ancient sea nymph,
一根白热的钢筋刺穿了
a white-hot steel pierced
我身体最深处的动脉; 你
the deepest artery of my being -- you.
你是个心脏手术师
You are a cardiac surgeon,
而我是你的心脏移植患者
and I am your transplant patient.
你淡定自若的站在我的胸前
And you stand poised over my chest,
握着我仍在跳动的心
holding my still-beating heart,
犹豫着, 等待着, 猜想着
hesitating, waiting, wondering.
所以我恳求你与我共进晚餐
So I implore you to join me for dinner,
或者是午餐, 如果你想随意点的话
or maybe lunch if you want to keep it casual,
下周五在蟹摊
next Friday at the crab shack.
我等待着你的回复
I await your response,
就如同山茶花等待着月亮的升起
as the camellia awaits the rise of the moon.
因为, 你了解, 类似晚上盛开之类的
'Cause, you know, it only blooms at night and stuff.
" 爱你的, 杰米 "
"Love, Jamie."
我认为杰米要约你出去--
I think Jamie is asking you out --
约会!
on a date!
没可能
Well, that ain't happening.
没戏
Nope.
为什么?
Why not?
石榴已经确定关系了
Garnet is already in a relationship.
等等, 真的?
Wait, really?
呃, 没错, 她就是个关系
Well, yeah. She is a relationship.
哦. 你是指, 因为她是个融合体
Oh, you mean, 'cause she's a fusion.
红宝石和蓝宝石是如此亲近
Ruby and Sapphire are so close
她们无法忍受分离
that they can't stand to be apart.
所以我猜与杰米的这次约会已经没有悬念了
So I guess this date with Jamie is out of the question.
三人成众
Three's a crowd.
但, 伙计们, 杰米花了如此多心思
But, guys, Jamie put so much thought
写的这封信!
into this letter!
如果不回复的话太粗鲁了!
It would be rude not to reply!
好吧, 石榴
Okay, Garnet,
也许用他的信的口吻写最好
it might be best to play off the tone of his letter
先用类似" 最亲爱的杰米 "开头
and start off with something like, "dearest Jamie."
好吧, 开始吧, 石榴
Okay, go for it, Garnet.
最开始是 "不"
Start with the letter "n."
好吧, 然后呢?
Okay. What next?
呃..."要"
Uh...The letter "o."
呃, 好吧
Uh, okay.
你可以直接把单词说出来, 而不是挨个字母拼
You can just say the whole word instead of spelling it out.
句号
Period.
所以,  "不" "要" "." ?
So, "n," "o," period?
噢...
Ohhh.
我认为我们得写得多点
I think we'll need more than that.
"没戏, 永远
"The end. Forever.
和永远的以后"
And even after that."
"你真诚的，石榴"
"Yours truly, Garnet."
嗯...
Hmm.
至少这个很真挚并且简练
At least it's honest and to the point.
你觉得他会在哪？
Where do you think he could be?
我不知道
I don't know.
他可能在派送邮件
He could be dropping off mail
满世界转悠
halfway around the world by now.
他在那！
There he is!
杰米
Jamie.
哦, 嘿, 康妮和史蒂文
Oh, hey, Connie and Steven.
你们来这里
You guys come out here
也是为了望着大海思考人生?
to stare at the ocean and think about life, too?
呃...不?
Uh...No?
我们来这里, 呃--
We came to, uh --
没错, 生活如疯
yeah. Life is crazy.
前一天, 你还在沙滩市配送邮件
One day, you're right here in Beach City, delivering mail,
接着你就发现
and then the next thing you know,
你在前往堪萨斯的巴士上
you're on a bus to Kansas
追寻你成为演员的梦想
following your dreams of becoming an actor.
"追寻你的梦想, " 他们说道
"Follow your dreams," they said.
但没人提起过
But no one said anything
前方需要面对的拒绝与忧伤
about all the rejection and sadness there was to be found.
日复一日的试镜
So many auditions day after day.
日复一日的被拒
So much rejection day after day.
这就是为什么我回来了
That's why I came back.
再有一个拒绝就会摧毁我幼小的内心
One more rejection would have destroyed my fragile heart.
对不起
Sorry.
有时我会不由自主的深沉装B, 你清楚吗?
Sometimes, I get caught up in the drama zone, you know?
没错, 深沉装B
Yeah, right. Drama zone.
哦, 既然这样, 我有个消息要给你--
Oh, by the way, we have something for y--
不, 我们没有!
no, we don't!
我们怎么能在现在把这封信给杰米呢?
How can we give this letter to Jamie now?
他很可能会伤心的
He might get upset.
我们能做点调整
We can make adjustments.
我们可以调整为杰米的诗意语言
We can match Jamie's poetic language
让他轻松的接受
and let him down easy.
我看过几集烂俗的肥皂剧
I watched some episodes of a torrid soap opera once,
所以我很自信能把握住浪漫的要领
so I'm confident that I get the gist of romance.
看!
There!
"亲爱的杰米...
"Dear Jamie...
你, 亲爱的山茶花,
You, dear camellia,
心怀期待的等待我如明月般的光亮,
expectantly await the light of my moon,
但我的光亮更似炙烤,
yet my light is more of a scorching,
让你枯萎, 如同沙漠热浪
wilting, dry desert heat.
而作为你比喻上的手术师
And as your metaphorical surgeon,
我怀着沉重的内心
it is with a heavy heart
敦促你寻找其他的人选
that I urge you to seek a second opinion.
我将心返还给你" --
I return your heart to you" --
"同时, 你头发很漂亮"
"also, your hair is nice."
"头发...很...
"Hair...Is...
漂亮
Nice.
你的, 但不属于你, 石榴"
Yours, but not really, Garnet."
完美
Perfect.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
此处背景音乐源自 "动物之森"
石榴!
Garnet!
汝何在, 我甜蜜, 炙烤的阳光?
Where art thou, my sweet scorching sunbeam?
哦, 不!
Oh, no!
石榴!
Garnet!
我阅读了汝信, 而我理解了!
I read thine letter, and I understand!
汝返还吾心!
Thou hast return eth mine heart!
啊?! 不, 那不是--
What?! No, that's not what --
石榴, 你喜欢着我的头发, 如我爱慕你的一样
Garnet, you like my hair just as I adore yours.
来到我的怀抱中吧, 石榴
Come to me, Garnet.
杰米!
Jamie!
啊, 少主史蒂文!
Ah, young master Steven!
赞美汝, 石榴女士何在?
Pray thee, where is lady Garnet?
她...
She...
她不--她不会来了
She's n-- she's not coming.
但我专门来此表明我对我的女人的爱意!
But I've come to proclaim my love for my woman!
不, 杰米, 你不了解! 我--
No, Jamie, you don't understand! I --
石榴! 你来了!
Garnet! You've come!
你可以告诉史蒂文所有的
You can tell Steven about all the beautiful things
你写给我的信件中的华丽辞藻
you wrote to me in your missive.
我可不是那么写的
I didn't write that.
但就在这里啊!
But it's all right here!
沾上了喜悦的泪水--现在还有雨水
Stained with tears of joy -- and now also rain.
是康妮和我写的, 杰米!
Connie and I wrote that letter, Jamie!
哈?
What?
我很抱歉, 杰米
I'm so sorry, Jamie.
我们只是想让你不要太伤心
We just wanted to let you down easy.
汝不愿炙烤吾, 吾之爱日?
Wilst thou not scorch me, my darling sun?
我不会, 以后也不会, 有兴趣
I am not, nor will I ever be, interested.
gun滚!
Go away!
我-我的小心脏啊!
M-my panache!
杰～米～!
Jamieeeee!
哦, 天哪
Oh, boy.
我真为可怜的杰米感到伤心
I feel so bad for poor Jamie.
没错, 但我确定他立刻就能走出这一切
Yeah. But I'm sure he'll bounce back from this in no time.
他随时都可能带着信件出现
He's probably gonna show up with the mail any moment now.
对啊
Yeah.
打扰一下, 小子们
Excuse me, kids.
我在寻找...
I'm looking for the home of...
史蒂文·宇宙的家?
Steven Universe?
我就是史蒂文·宇宙的家
I'm the home of Steven Universe.
嘿, 你是格雷格的孩子
Hey, you're Greg's boy.
我以为杰米在开玩笑
I thought Jamie was pulling my leg
他之前说你就住在这里
when he told me you were living over here.
等等, 那杰米呢?
W-wait. Where is Jamie?
啊, 那个可怜的孩子完全崩溃了
Aw, that poor kid's emotions have been destroyed.
什么?!
What?!
没错, 他简直一团糟!
Yeah, he's a mess!
他说自己无法承受再次往这里送邮件了
Said he couldn't bear to deliver mail on this route again
自从他被拒绝后
after having his love spurned.
他这么说的
He said it just like this.
就像--就像, 当他深沉的装B时
Like -- like, when he's in the drama zone.
接着他握紧了自己的拳头, 闭上了眼睛, 像这样
Then he clenched his fist and closed his eyes like this.
真是装B一绝啊
Full of drama to the end.
不管怎样, 这里是一本折扣券
Anyway, here's a book of coupons.
祝好!
Have a good one!
你看起来很伤心
You look sad.
我们这次真的搞砸了
We really messed up this time.
因为我们, 杰米前所未有的低沉
Because of us, Jamie's feeling lower than ever.
我们粉碎了他的意志!
We've shattered the man!
他不会再爱了
He'll never love again!
我会跟他谈谈的
I'll go talk to him.
但你的言语会摧毁他的!
But your words will destroy him!
你能不能, 像是, 擦除他的大脑
Can't you just, like, zap his brain
然后他就不会记得这一切?
so he forgets any of this ever happened?
杰米
Jamie.
石榴
Garnet.
我不是要伤你的心
I didn't mean to upset you.
那么你愿意和我约吗?
Then will you go out with me?
不!
No!
但我自从看到你的那一刻就爱上你的
But I've loved you since the moment I saw you.
一见钟情并不存在
Love at first sight doesn't exist.
爱需要时间, 还有精力
Love takes time, and love takes work.
再怎么说, 至少你也得了解另一半
At the very least, you have to know the other person.
而你真的不清楚我到底是什么
And you literally have no idea who or what I am.
但我为你盛开了, 就像--就像月光下的山茶花
But I bloom for you, like -- like a camellia under moonlight.
不, 你没有!
No, you don't!
你假扮了一个热恋中的蠢蛋
You make a very convincing lovesick fool.
你骗到了这两个孩子
You convinced these children.
你甚至骗了自己
You even convinced yourself.
你是个非常好的演员
You're a fantastic actor.
那我现在该做什么?
What am I supposed to do now?
从本地剧院开始
Start with local theater.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
那些建议含金量很高
That was some pretty solid advice.
那些是你写给石榴的信吗?
Were those more letters you wrote to Garnet?
不, 那些只是邮件
No, that was the mail
我本该将这些信件送达的
I was supposed to deliver on my last route.
我们会帮你收集的
We'll help you pick it all up.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果我可以做到
♪ If I could begin to be
你对我期望的一半
♪ half of what you think of me
我愿意做任何事
♪ I could do about anything
我愿学会像你一样，去爱
♪ I could even learn how to love like you ♪